You didn't think this was the end of the story, did you?
Descendants 3 is a family, tv movie, adventure film directed by Kenny Ortega.
The teenagers of Disney's most infamous villains return to the Isle of the Lost to
recruit a new batch of villainous offspring to join them at Auradon Prep.
Mal, played by Dove Cameron.
Ben, played by Mitchell Hope.
Carlos, played by Cameron Boyce.
Evie, played by Sofia Carson.
Harry Hook, played by Thomas Doherty.
Chad, played by Jedidiah Goodacre.
Descendants 3 is an American musical fantasy television film directed by
Kenny Ortega, and written by Sara Parriott and Josann McGibbon.
It is a sequel to Descendants 2 (2017), and the third installment in the Descendants
franchise, while being the last film focused on Mal (Dove Cameron) and her friends.
It also stars Cameron Boyce, Sofia Carson, Booboo Stewart,
Cheyenne Jackson, China Anne McClain, and Sarah Jeffery.
The film premiered on Disney Channel on August 2, 2019, and in other
territories worldwide starting on October 12, 2019.
It was followed by an animated television special, Descendants: The Royal Wedding, released in 2021, while
a fourth film focusing on new characters, Descendants: The Rise of Red, premiered in 2024.
The film explores themes of magic, musical, family.